Guide to the Edward Bradford Titchener papers,1887-1940.
Titchener, Edward Bradford papers, 1887-1940
- Correspondence
  - Karl Dallenbach to EBT, 10/31/25 (Box 7)
  - Karl Dallenbach to EBT, 11/2/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 11/2/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 11/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 11/3/25 (Box 7)
  - Karl Dallembach to EBT, 11/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. B. Weld, 11/5/25 (Box 7)
  - Harry Heisen to EBT, 11/6/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to "H", 11/6/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 11/6/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach (form letter), 11/10/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Paul Young, 11/10/25 (Box 7)
  - Karl Dalleribach to EBT, 11/12/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor William S. Adams, 11/12/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. R. Orndorff, 11/12/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Max Wertheimer, 11/13/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macadllan Co. (end. analysis of book), 11/13/25 (Box 7)
  - C. A. Ruckmick to EBT, 11/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Superintendent of Schools, Oakland, California., 11/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Joseph Holmers, 11/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. Boyd, 11/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor F. Stuart Chapin, 11/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Gold Rose Printing Co., 11/16/25 (Box 7)
  - Edward S. Robinson to EBT, 11/17/25 (Box 7)
  - S. Feraberger to EBE, 11/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor K. Koffka, 11/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. Clapareck, 11/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. W. K. Matthews, 11/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 11/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Gasper Cruy, 11/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Gardner Murphy, 11/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Philip Johnson, 11/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelling, 11/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Kelson, 11/18/25 (Box 7)
  - John P. Nafe to EBT, 11/19/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. 0. Boring, 11/19/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Charles H. Ward, 11/19/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Harold Hall, 11/19/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. C. A. Dickinson, 11/19/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 11/20/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas L. Elder, 11/20/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor William Schiever, 11/20/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor R. Orndorff, 11/20/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Edward S. Robinson, 11/20/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith of the MacmUlan Co., 11/20/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Philip Johnson, 11/20/25 (Box 7)
  - Margaret Floy Washburn To EBT, 11/21/25 (Box 7)
  - W. B. Pillsbury to EBB, 11/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. Weld, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Maud A. Merill, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. R. Kantor, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to G. H. Stoelting, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to A. L. Kroeber, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Max Kohl, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. L. Thorndike, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mrs. Hutter, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. L. Thorndike, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to G. T. Line, 11/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Margaret Floy Washburn, 11/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 11/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J.P.Nafe, 11/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Nutrition Laboratory, 11/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr. Loudder Klyce, 11/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mrs. H. Piotrowaka, 11/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. S. H. Self, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to the Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to William Hesslein, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. Weld, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor S. G. Boring, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Merl L. Reid, 11/25/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Charles H. Ward, 11/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor L. N. Wilson, 11/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to W. W. Wideman, 11/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr Elsie Murray, 11/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to William C. Foster, 11/27/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. P. WaM, 11/30/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith, The Macmillan Co., 11/30/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Madison Bentley, 11/30/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. Heinrich, 11/30/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to M. Wroblewski, 11/30/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Messrs Longmans, Green and Co., 12/1/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Rowena Morse, 12/2/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. G. J. Rich, 12/2/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. K. L. Bixley, 12/2/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. C. Warren, 12/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rowland Wood, 12/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 12/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 12/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Charles H. Ward, 12/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Woolsey, 12/3/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 12/V25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. Strunk, 12/4/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Chiao Tsai, 12/4/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langgeld, 12/7/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 12/7/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Prank Angell, 12/8/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Charles H. Ward, 12/9/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 12/9/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr. Horigichi, 12/9/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. A. Heggie and Bro. Co., 12/9/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Abner B. Brown, 12/9/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 12/11/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 12/11/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 12/11/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 12/11/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Margaret Trimble, 12/11/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 12/14/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 12/14/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professoe Frank Lillie, 12/14/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor M. 0. Wilson, 12/14/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. E. Treman, 12/14/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Albert Schinz, 12/14/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. BORING, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. G. H. Taylor, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Horiguchi, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Karl Dallenbach, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor K. C. Mookherzi, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Kluver, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor George T. Avery, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J.P. Nafe, 12/15/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 12/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Charles H. Ward, 12/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. M. Johnson, 12/16/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Walter F. Wetto, 12/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. M. Johnson, 12/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor A. L. Kroeber, 12/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. H. Stoelting, 12/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. E. W. Gifford, 12/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 12/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor William S. Adams, 12/17/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Abner E. Brown, 12/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor L. L. Bernard, 12/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Feldman, 12/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Poynder, 12/18/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 12/21/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Walter F. Webb, 12/21/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr. Sidney P. Hoe, 12/21/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor James P. C. Southall, 12/21/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to George Rogalsky, 12/21/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 12/21/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. H. Burnham, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Ruth Travers, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dimnick, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. P. Andrews, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to University Library, 12/22/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Fraulein Eleonore Wundt, 12/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 12/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. T. Lines, 12/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Johann Barth, 12/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Tomokichi Horiguchi, 12/23/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Walter Webb, 12/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 12/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. D. Sheldon, 12/24//25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 12/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. B. Weld, 12/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Charles Howard, 12/24/25 (Box 7)
  - EBT to American Lead Pencil Co., 12/24/25 (Box 7)
  - Extract from "God of Night" by Elias Tobenkin, 1925 (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts of two book reviews, 1925 (Box 7)
  - A questionnaire concerning an un-named party, 1925 (Box 7)
  - List of Roman coins for sale and photographs, 1925 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 1/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 1/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to C. Ladd-Franklin, 1/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 1/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Abe Mansbach, 1/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 1/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dean S. W. Reaves, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Marbe, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Johann A. Barth, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Foster (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor John E. Anderson, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Samuel Hayes, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Samuel W. Fernberger, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor P. T. Young, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Ida M. Mellen, 1/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Daya Ram Sahni, 1/6/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. E. Van Natta, 1/6/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 1/6/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Messrs. Howell andt Howell, 1/6/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor C. M. S. Mid jo, 1/6/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 1/6/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. T. Lines, 1/7/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 1/7/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 1/7/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to the Corner Book Store, 1/7/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 1/7/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. C. Warren, 1/7/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Latham, 1/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to the Brandow printing Co., 1/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Helen K. Mull, 1/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Sheperd Dawson, 1/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. A. H. Smith, 1/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Andor Juhasy, 1/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. G. Bishop, 1/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Weld, 1/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Paul T. Young, 1/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mansbach Cigar Co., 1/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 1/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Edith L. Elliott, 1/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 1/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Max von Frey, 1/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Poynder, 1/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to American College Bureau, 1/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to George de Grassi, 1/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to professor Robert H, Gault, 1/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Walter Webb, 1/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Weld, 1/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Edith L. Elliot, 1/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Department of Interior, 1/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 1/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Raymond Dodge, 1/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 1/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Samuel Ferribepger, 1/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Janes Clapham, 1/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Sargents, 1/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Audrey M. Shuey, 1/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor R. A. TSanoff, 1/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor S. W. Ferriberger, 1/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Max Meeney, 1/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to G. A. Poynder, 1/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith of The Macmillan Company, 1/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Martin Reymert, 1/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Hcwland Wood, 1/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 1/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to American Library Association, 1/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Thomas Elder, 1/20/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 1/20/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to MR.. G. T. Lines, 1/20/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor A. J. Snow, 1/20/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. W. Nelson, 1/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 1/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor S. W. Femberger, 1/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor S. G. Boring, 1/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Philip Johnson, 1/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 1/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 1/28/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Fabrikant, 1/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Frederick S. Ryman, 1/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 1/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to College Entrance Examnation Board, 1/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss R. S. Maimed, 1/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. Kluver, 1/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Southern Teacher's Agency, 2/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas L. Elder, 2/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. S. Moore, 2/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 2/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dimmick, 2/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. T. Lines, 2/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas L Elder, 2/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor M. J. Zigler, 2/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 2/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. J. Beal, 2/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. A. Esper, 2/k/Z6 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 2/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Bowers, 2/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Lillian Hatfield, 2/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckndck, 2/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. 0. Houser, 2/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 2/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 2/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ru.ckmick, 2/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Jared S. Moore, 2/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Curt Rosenow, 2/28/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. A. Heggie and Bros. Co., 2/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Ogden, 2/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Fabrikant, 2/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Willcox, 2/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 2/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 2/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 2/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Ogden, 2/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Annetta Clark, 2/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 2/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelling, 2/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Judge Frank Irvine, 2/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 2/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 2/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. W. Sailor, 2/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 2/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 2/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to M. S. Scheck, 2/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor M. L. Reymert, 2/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 2/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 2/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 2/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 2/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Charles Hull, 2/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. W. R. Miles, 2/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr.L. R. G. Crandon, 2/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Seiji Honsho, 2/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Tomi Wada untitled letter, 2/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 2/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Holland Wood, 2/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Douglas Fryer, 2/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Max Kohl, 2/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Zigler, 2/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to New York Life Insurance Co., 2/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 2/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor C. Spearman, 2/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 2/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 2/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Alfred Gordon, 2/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to American College Bureau, 2/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 2/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 3/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 3/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor Raymond Dodge, 3/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor W. Caldwell, 3/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 3/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor R. A. Tsanoff, 3/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Douglas Fryer, 3/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Frank Angell, 3/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. D. J. Lilleman, 3/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to ¥. H. Valentine, 3/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 3/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to President of Goucher College, 3/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EEP to Howland Wood, 3/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 3/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Leitz, 3/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckndck, 3/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 3/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. E. S. Rudisill, 3/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. A. Tsanoff, 3/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 3/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor D. C. Rogers, 3/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to 3. H. Self (circular) letter, 3/23/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 3/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 3/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor D. C. Rogers, 3/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 3/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Alice H. Sullivan, 3/29/26 (Box 7)
  - Circular letter from Committee of Five hundred, 3/30/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. J. H. Taylor, 3/31/26 (Box 7)
  - Questionaire from Department of Psychology, Columbia University, March 1926 (Box 7)
  - EBP to J. P. Guilford, 4/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EEP to Professor S. W. Fernberger, 4/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Honorary Secretary, British Psychological Society, 4/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. G. Bishop, 4/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 4/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rothschild, 4/16/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to President Lowell of Harvard University, 4/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 4/20/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. G. Bishop, 4/20/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor David C. Rogers, 4/20/26 (Box 7)
  - Professor H. G. Bishop to EBT, 4/23/26 (Box 7)
  - M. J. Zigler to EBT, 4/27/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor David Rogers, 4/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. G. Bishop, 4/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 5/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. M. Ogden, 5/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to D. C. Rogers, 5/7/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dimnick, 5/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 5/10/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss E. T. Chen, 5/10/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to D. C. Rogers, 5/10/2$ (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. G. Bishop, 5/12/26 (Box 7)
  - M. J. Zigler to EBT, 5/12/26 (Box 7)
  - M. J. Zigler to EBT, 5/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. D. Sheldon, 5/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogdeh, 5/13/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. L. dements, 5/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. Barrett, 5/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBB to R. M. Ogden, 5/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to "H", 5/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professot E. G. Boring, 5/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Guilford, 5/20/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 5/21/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to W. H. Valentine, 5/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. P. H. Ward, 5/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 5/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor F. E. Fisk, 5/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor J. B. Miner, 5/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 5/28/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor M. L. Reymert, 6/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. H. Ward, 6/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Dorothy Barstow, 6/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 6/3/26 (Box 7)
  - Thomas Elder to EBT, 7/12/26 (Box 7)
  - Thomas Elder to EBT, 7/28/26 (Box 7)
  - F. Lowell Bixley to EBT (end. statement of account), 8/16/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 8/17/26 (Box 7)
  - Blank letter of recommendation, 8/28/26 (Box 7)
  - Fernberger to EBT, 9/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. F. Aveling, 9/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 9/26/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dean W. Clark Trow, 9/30/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howled Wood, 9/30/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi, 10/1/26 (Box 7)
  - R. W. Sellars to The Macmillan Company, 10/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Florence Woolsey, 10/13/26 (Box 7)
  - Sadazi Takaki to EBT, 10/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to P. H. Ward, 10/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. Trigant Borrow, 10/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 10/22/26 (Box 7)
  - Thomas Elder to EBT, 10/23/26 (Box 7)
  - Roy Sellars to the Maemillan Company, 10/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 10/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor R. A. Tsanoff, 10/25/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. Weld, 10/25/26 (Box 7)
  - G. M. Patrick to Professor Roy Wood Sellara, 10/28/26 (Box 7)
  - Williaam Davis to EBT, 10/29/26 (Box 7)
  - Mr.. D. Griffin to EBT, 10/29/26 (Box 7)
  - B. W. Sellars to The Maemillan Company, 10/30/26 (Box 7)
  - Form letter from Edith Elliot of the national Research Council, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - Form letter from Willard Straight Hall, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mrs. Ann A. Weelans, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. Patten-Saunders, 11/1/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 11/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to G de Grassi, 11/2/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The President, Cornell University, 11/2/26 (Box 7)
  - Robert Moton to EBT, 11/3/26 (Box 7)
  - B. H. Blackwell to EBT, 11/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 11/3/20 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The President, Cornell University, 11/3/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mrs. Baker, 11/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mrs. Louise Freeman, 11/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 11/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 11/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor R. H. Gautt, 11/4/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to L. H. Wilson, 11/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 11/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Florence Woolsey, 11/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Frances fells, 11/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to D. Griffin, 11/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. S. Feldman, 11/5/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 11/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Wundt, 11/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Bans C. Syz, 11/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Gustav Fock, 11/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. Weld, 11/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to R. H. Jordan, 11/8/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Harold Flack, 11/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Prank, 11/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dean of Graduate School, 11/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to George Rogalsky, 11/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Bostwick, 11/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 11/9/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 11/10/26 (Box 7)
  - Florence B. Woolsey to EBT, 11/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. H. M. Johnson, 11/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor R. H. Gautt, 11/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to K. F. Koehlers, 11/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Frank Ward, 11/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to L. Carmichael, 11/11/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Co., 11/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Miss Frances Wells, 11/12/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 11/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Tice and Lynch, 11/15/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 11/16/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Ladazi Takaki, 11/16/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 11/16/26 (Box 7)
  - H. S. Latham to EBT, 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. B. N. Dorcas, 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Mr.. Patterson, 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Bostwick, 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to National Geographic Society, 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to "F", 11/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 11/18/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 11/18/26 (Box 7)
  - S. Feldman to EBT, 11/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to President, Cornell University, 11/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 11/19/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Professor H. H. Goddard, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Emeline Moul, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. C. J. Warden, 11/22/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 11/23/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 11/24/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 11/29/26 (Box 7)
  - B. H. Blackwell to EBT, 11/29/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr. S. Feldman, 11/29/26 (Box 7)
  - E. S. Robinson to EBT, 11/30/26 (Box 7)
  - Manuscript of a book review, 1926 (Box 7)
  - "Dear Florence", 1926 (Box 7)
  - Form for Biographical Dictionary of American Men of Science, 1926 (Box 7)
  - Memorandum, 1926 (Box 7)
  - List of coin dealers, 1926 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 12/2/26 (Box 7)
  - Harry Helson to EBT, 12/2/26 (Box 7)
  - Howland Wood to EBT, 12/2/26 (Box 7)
  - Martin Reymert to EBT, 12/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 12/6/25 (Box 7)
  - E. Prances Wells to EBT, 12/6/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 12/7/26 (Box 7)
  - Florence B. Woolsey to EBT, 12/8/26 (Box 7)
  - J. P. Nafe to EBT, 12/9/26 (Box 7)